<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MobileMeApp</string>
    <string name="WScreen">Hi, my name is Ahmed and I like to play video games,
        enjoy some football with my friends or just take a long walk down the beach in my free time.
    </string>
    <string name="PScreen">
        I am currently a 3rd year university student studying for a degree in Software and Internet Technologies
        in the Technical University of Varna. I became interested in programming, because of video games,
        but once I started learning programming I saw there is more to that than video games.
        I have only 1 calculator made on android project and not much experience with java .
        I am more experienced with c++ , but still I am just a beginner in any language really.
        Experience comes with time and I believe I will be experienced in couple of years in at least
        1 programming language.
        I would describe myself as a highly motivated to pursue a career in Software Engineering
        and open for knowledge type of person. I don\'t have much knowledge in the field of Programming
        ,but nonetheless I am really passionate about it.

    </string>
    <string name="MScreen">
        I am motivated to work, because as every young person I want to have my own place
        in this world. I want to learn programming so I can make software that one day
        will be used and helpful for the users and hopefully make their life easier,
        but also something that will be useful for the users. That will make me feel
        that I am helping this world with small steps every day. Also money is another
        motivation, but for that I need experience and knowledge I still do not possess
        and that\'s what I want for now to become a good programmer in 5-10 years.
        To learn company level standards to software building and testing.
        I applied for an Internship in FlatRock ,
        because I felt I wanted to broaden my knowledge by experiencing how the workflow is in
        a big company. I really want one day to become a good programmer and solve problems.
        I decided to apply for Android Internship, because with technologies referring to mobile
        devices, smart watches and anything we carry everywhere in our daily lives being
        available to more people than ever before , the need for software solutions on these devices
        is more than ever before and I feel like I want to be part of the making of these
        software solutions.

    </string>
</resources>